{"data":[{"question":"He hasn't finished yet ______ he?","a":"has","b":"hasn't","c":"does","d":"did","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"You go to London every day, ______ you?","a":"don't","b":"won't","c":"can't","d":"aren't","answer":"1","explain":"- Tag question structure:\u00a0\n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- If the statement doesn't use an auxiliary verb, then the auxiliary do is used in the tag part","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"You couldn't come tomorrow, ______ you?","a":"could","b":"couldn't","c":"did","d":"were","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n+ If a modal (can, could, will, should, etc.) is used in the statement, then the same modal is used in the tag part","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"He died at the ______ 82.","a":"years","b":"years old","c":"age of","d":"age","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Structure: age + of + number to mention the year- old","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"You weren't at the meeting, ______ you?","a":"were","b":"are","c":"have","d":"do","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+Positive statement, nagative tag? \n+ Nagative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"There were many people, ______ there?","a":"were","b":"weren't","c":"aren't","d":"are","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"You haven't got a camera, _______ you?","a":"haven't","b":"have","c":"do","d":"will","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"You come here often,_______ you?","a":"come","b":"do","c":"don't","d":"haven't","answer":"3","explain":"- Tag question structure:\u00a0\n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"Jenny's in Italy, ______ she?","a":"doesn't","b":"isn't","c":"aren't","d":"hasn't","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"},{"question":"She doesn't live here, ______ she?","a":"doesn't","b":"will","c":"does","d":"did","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Tag question structure: \n+ Positive statement, negative tag? \n+ Negative statement, positive tag? \n- The verb in the statement should be the same tense as the verb in the tag \n- If the verb used in the statement is an auxiliary verb, then the verb used in the tag must match it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"70","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"1"}]}